Guide to the Richard C. Bell Drawings and Other Materials
Richard C. Bell Drawings and Other Materials
- Drawings, 1924-2004
  - RDU Center: RDU Airport (1 of 3), 1994 (Tube 410)
    Site plans, planting plan, irrigation plan, construction details, topographic survey, landscape planting plan
    Burnstudio Architects; Bell-Glazener Design Group; Morrisville (N.C.)
  - RDU Center: RDU Airport (2 of 3), 1994 (Tube 411)
  - RDU Center: RDU Airport (3 of 3), 1994 (Tube 412)
    Topographic survey, sketches
  - Recreation and Maintenance Facilities (1 of 2), 1972 (Tube 52)
  - Recreation and Maintenance Facilities (2 of 2), 1972 (Tube 690)
  - Redd (Jane and Warren) property, 1976 (Tube 571)
    Boundary survey
  - Redd (Mr. and Mrs. Warren and Mr. F. Marion) residences, 1982-1983 (Tube 717)
    Schematic Site Plans, Planting Plan, Grading Plans, Perspective Sketch of Office Condominiums, Master Plan Showing Land Use of Property, Land Use Study, Study of Albemarle Road Area, Land Use Plan and Boundary Survey for Rezoning Request
  - Reeves (Mr. and Mrs. C.E., Jr.) residence (1 of 2), 1968 (Tube 64)
    Staking plan, planting plan, landscape details, lighting plan, landscape plan
  - Reeves (Mr. and Mrs. C.E., Jr.) residence (2 of 2), 1968 (Tube 67)
  - Reid Street parking area, 1998 (Tube 62)
  - Renaissance, 1995 (Tube 478)
    Illustrative site plan
  - Renaissance, 1993 (Tube 503)
    Illustrative Site Plan of Development within Sunnyside Neighborhood, Building Elevation
    Bell-Glazener Design Group; David Hall Associates, Inc.; Winston-Salem (N.C.)
  - Renaissance: Commerical/Retail center, 1993-1995 (Tube 66)
    Illustrative site plan of development within Sunnyside neighborhood
  - Renaissance Park, 1993 (Tube 67)
    Plan showing relationship of development to southeast area, land plan for Arista Mills property
  - Renaissance Place, 1993-1994 (Tube 475)
    Land use plan for Arista Mills property, illustrative site plan, development to southeast area
  - Research Triangle Foundation of North Carolina (Tube 62)
    Concept plan
  - Research Triangle Institute: Hill Building, 1977 (Tube 322)
    Bell Design Group; Six Associates, Inc.; Research Triangle Park (N.C.)
  - Research Triangle Institute Campus (Tube 116)
    Land forms
  - Research Triangle Institute Campus (Tube 352)
  - Research Triangle Park Map, 1980-1987 (Tube 551)
    Topographic Map with Roads
    Landmark Engineering Co., Inc.; Durham (N.C.)
  - Research Triangle Park Map, 1996 (Tube 145)
    Envirotek, Inc.; Research Triangle Park (N.C.)
  - Residential Village, 1993 (Tube 494)
  - Ritchie (Fred and Pat) residence, 1989 (Tube 762)
    Bell-Glazener Design Group; Arthur Manns Harden Architects; Pinehurst (N.C.)
  - River Ridge Run, 1974-1976 (Tube 32)
  - River Ridge Run, 1973-1976 (Tube 33)
  - River Ridge Run, 1975 (Tube 34)
  - Rivers East Condominiums, 1973 (Tube 652)
    Concrete dividers, panels plan, lighting plan, preliminary grading plan, staking plan, site construction details
    Bell Design Group; Willis James B. Jr.; New Bern (N.C.)
  - Roanoke Island Memorial Gardens, 1965-1967 (Tube 202)
    Monument details, staking plans, master plan
  - Roaring Gap (Tube 58)
    Roaring Gap (N.C.)
  - Roaring Gap Club (1 of 2), 1978 (Tube 300)
  - Roaring Gap Club (2 of 2), 1978 (Tube 844)
    Landscape Development Plan, Site Plan, Existing Land Use
  - Roaring Gap Club (1 of 2), 1971-1978 (Tube 290)
    Proposed mountain homes, new clubhouse facilities
    Richard C. Bell Associates; Bell Design Group; Roaring Gap (N.C.)
  - Roaring Gap Club (2 of 2), 1971-1978 (Tube 69)
    Site development plans, new clubhouse and facilities, proposed mountain homes, feasibility designs, landscape development plan
    Richard C. Bell Associates; Flynn Ligon B. AIA; Bell Design Group; Hicks Mason S.; Roaring Gap (N.C.)
  - Roaring Gap Club: Bird's eye perspective of proposed mountain homes, 1978 (Tube 16)
  - Roaring Gap Club, Inc., 1970-1972 (Tube 289)
  - Roaring Gap Club, Inc.: New clubhouse and facilities, 1972 (Tube 710)
    Richard C. Bell Associates; Roaring Gap (N.C.)
  - Roaring Gap Company, 1950 (Tube 835)
    Graystone Inn First Floor Plan, Graystone Inn Second Floor Plan, Bryans Knob & Village Property Maps, Detail Plan of Lot Arrangement
    Grinnell Company; Roaring Gap (N.C.)
  - Roaring Gap Country Club (Tube 799)
    Surveys, Site Studies
    Scott David B. CLS; Alleghany County (N.C.)
  - Roaring Gap: Site plan, 1972 (Tube 282)
  - Robbins (Mr. and Mrs. Bill) residence (1 of 2), 1974 (Tube 478)
  - Robbins (Mr. and Mrs. Bill) residence (2 of 2), 1974 (Tube 477)
    Site development
    Bell Design Group; NewKirk Haywood; Atlantic Beach (N.C.)
  - Robeson County Public Library, 1967-1968 (Tube 66)
    Change order no. 3, lighting plan, landscape development plan
    Richard C. Bell Associates; Lee Elizabeth B.; Lumberton (N.C.)
  - Robeson County Public Library, 1968 (Tube 67)
    Storm drainage plan, staking plan
    Lee Elizabeth B.; Richard C. Bell Associates; Lumberton (N.C.)
  - Rockwell Manufacturing Company, 1969 (Tube 160)
    G. Milton Small & Associates; Richard C. Bell Associates; Raleigh (N.C.)
  - Rocky Branch Outfall: City of Raleigh, 1974 (Tube 459)
    Construction Plans (Pullen Park Drive)
    Lovett & Bunn, Inc.; J. Fred Davis, Jr., Inc.; Raleigh (N.C.)
  - Romanek (Henry and Betsy) residence, 1974-1984 (Tube 63)
    Japanese garden planting plan, staking plan, grading plan, exterior elevation, proposal 3
    Bell Design Group; Nash County (N.C.)
  - Rose (Tom and Joanne) residence and grounds (1 of 3), 1976-1977 (Tube 48)
    Site Development
  - Rose (Tom and Joanne) residence and grounds (2 of 3), 1976-1977 (Tube 48)
  - Rose (Tom and Joanne) residence and grounds (3 of 3), 1976-1977 (Tube 650)
    Land use, typical sections, suggested kitchen layout, elevations, deck details
  - Rose (Tom and Joanne) residence and grounds, 1976 (Tube 649)
    Staking and grading, site development, floor plans, sections, heating and air condition
  - Rose (Tom and Joanne) residence and grounds (Tube 283)
    Bird's-eye perspective
    Lasater-Hopkins; Bell Design Group; Chapel Hill (N.C.)
  - Rosemary Baptist Church: Master site development, 1964 (Tube 37)
    Richard C. Bell Associates; Roanoke Rapids (N.C.)
  - Rosemary Plant: J.P. Stevens & Co., 1965 (Tube 49)
  - Rosenthal (Susan and Michael Hershfield) residence (1 of 2), 2001 (Tube 137)
  - Rosenthal (Susan and Michael Hershfield) residence (2 of 2), 2001 (Tube 398)
    Site plans, topographic survey, staking and grading plan, enlarged plan - deck detail, plans and elevations
  - Rosenthal (Susan and Michael Hershfield) residence (1 of 3), 2002 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Floor Plans, Site Plans
    Harmon Frank 1941-; Bell-Glazener-Jenkins Planning; Hillsborough (N.C.)
  - Rosenthal (Susan and Michael Hershfield) residence (2 of 3), 2002 (Tube 250)
    Lighting Plan
  - Rosenthal (Susan and Michael Hershfield) residence (3 of 3), 2002 (Tube 805)
    Irrigation plan
  - Rosenthal (Susan and Michael Hershfield) residence (1 of 3), 2001-2002 (Tube 249)
    Landscape development plan, lighting details, site plan
  - Rosenthal (Susan and Michael Hershfield) residence (2 of 3), 2001-2002 (Tube 397)
    Site plan, plans and elevations, landscape development plan, enlarged plan - deck detail
  - Rosenthal (Susan and Michael Hershfield) residence (3 of 3), 2001-2002 (Tube 399)
    Enlarged plan - deck detail, site plan, topographic survey, lighting plan, landscape development plan
  - Rosenthal (Susan and Michael Hershfield) residence (1 of 2), 2001-2003 (Tube 242)
    Site plan, lighting plan, elevations, irrigation plan, staking and grading plan, landscape development plan
  - Rosenthal (Susan and Michael Hershfield) residence (2 of 2), 2001-2003 (Tube 243)
    Lighting plan, irrigation plan, topographic and boundary survey
  - Rosenthal/Hershfield residence (1 of 2), 2000-2002 (Tube 769)
    Site Plans, Floor Plans
  - Rosenthal/Hershfield residence (2 of 2), 2000-2002 (Tube 764)
    Survey, Elevations, Floor Plans, Bedroom Options, Kitchen Options, Bedroom Sections, Site Plans
    Land Surveys, Inc.; Harmon Frank 1941-; Bell-Glazener-Jenkins Planning; Hillsborough (N.C.)
  - Rosenthal/Hershfield residence, 2001 (Tube 766)
  - Rowland (Joe) estate: Somerhill (1 of 2), 1986-1995 (Tube 147)
    Staking and grading plans, landscape development plans
    Bell-Glazener Design Group; Bell Design Group; Chapel Hill (N.C.)
  - Rowland (Joe) estate: Somerhill (2 of 2), 1986-1995 (Tube 148)
    Landscape development plans, master plan, lighting plan, irrigation plan, planting plan
    Bell-Glazener Design Group; Bell Design Group; Hausler Werner; Chapel Hill (N.C.)
  - Rowland (Joe) estate: Somerhill (1 of 2), 1995-1998 (Tube 414)
    Topographic survey, residential development plan, aerial photograph, master landscape plan, enlarged entrance plan
  - Rowland (Joe) estate: Somerhill (2 of 2), 1995-1998 (Tube 415)
    Elevations, floor plans, enlarged plan at house, residential development plan, enlarged entrance plan
    Bell-Glazener Design Group; Szostak Philip AIA; Orange County (N.C.)
  - Rowland (Joe) estate: Somerhill (1 of 2), 1997 (Tube 765)
    Bell-Glazener Design Group; Szostak Philip AIA; Hillsborough (N.C.)
  - Rowland (Joe) estate: Somerhill (2 of 2), 1997 (Tube 508)
  - Rowland (Joe) estate: Somerhill, 1995 (Tube 149)
    Floor plans, roof plan, elevations, wall sections, foundation information
    Szostak Philip AIA; Hillsborough (N.C.)
  - Rowland (Joe) estate: Somerhill, 1995-1997 (Tube 115)
    Bell-Glazener Design Group; Hillsborough (N.C.)
  - Rowland (Joe) estate: Somerhill, 1996-1997 (Tube 107)
    Site development plan, enlarged plan at house
    Szostak Philip AIA; Bell-Glazener Design Group; Hillsborough (N.C.)
  - Rowland (Joe) estate: Somerhill (Tube 132)
    Topographic survey, floor plans
  - Runnymeade Road area (Tube 875)
  - Saint Andrews Condominiums, 1981 (Tube 477)
    Staking plan, construction details, planting plan, grading plan
    Bell Design Group; Taylor Township (N.C.)
  - Saint George Place at Bermuda Run (1 of 2), 1987 (Tube 181)
  - Saint George Place at Bermuda Run (2 of 2), 1987 (Tube 380)
  - Saint George Place at Bermuda Run, 1986-1987 (Tube 186)
    Sediment and Erosion Control, general staking plan, typical fences, railings, steps, brick walls
  - Saint Luke's Hospital, Inc., 1982 (Tube 437)
    Master development plan, existing conditions map
    Richard C. Bell Associates; Bell Design Group; Polk County (N.C.)
  - Saint Mary's College, 1966-1992 (Flatfolder 15)
    Library floor plans, site layout
    McKimmon and Rogers; Raleigh (N.C.)
  - Saint Mary's College, 1970-1992 (Tube 479)
    Classroom building, tree assessment plan
    Bell-Glazener Design Group; McKimmon and Rogers; Raleigh (N.C.)
  - Saint Mary's College, 1971-1995 (Tube 136)
    Site development plans for new facility
  - Saint Mary's College (1 of 6), 1989 (Tube 365)
    Site plans, site plan at Ravenscroft House, plantings, landscape plan at bishop's residence
    Bell-Glazener Design Group; McKimmon, Edwards, & Shawcroft; Raleigh (N.C.)
  - Saint Mary's College (2 of 6), 1989 (Tube 366)
    Planting plan, electrical, elevation, site plan at Ravenscroft House, irrigation plan, landscape plan at bishop's residence
    McKimmon, Edwards, & Shawcroft; Bell-Glazener Design Group; Raleigh (N.C.)
  - Saint Mary's College (3 of 6), 1989 (Tube 618)
    Site Plans, Site Plans (Base), Site Plan at Ravenscroft House
  - Saint Mary's College (4 of 6), 1989 (Tube 619)
  - Saint Mary's College (5 of 6), 1989 (Tube 620)
    Enlargements of Site Plans with Topographic Details
  - Saint Mary's College (6 of 6), 1989 (Tube 621)
    Enlargements, Master Plan Grid
  - Saint Mary's College, 1989-1990 (Tube 367)
    Sesquicentennial project areas, irrigation, electrical, elevation, lighting and storm drainage
  - Saint Mary's College (1 of 4), 1989-1992 (Tube 654)
    Plot Plan, Site Plan, Landscape Planting Plan
  - Saint Mary's College (2 of 4), 1989-1992 (Tube 660)
    Landscape Plan of Bishop's residence, Grading and Staking Plan, Site Plans, Detail of Portico and Fountain, Relocation of Dean of Students residence Site Plan, Details and Elevations, Site Plan at Ravenscroft House
  - Saint Mary's College (3 of 4), 1989-1992 (Tube 661)
    Irrigation Plans, Site Plan Enlargements
  - Saint Mary's College (4 of 4), 1989-1992 (Tube 658)
    North Central Campus Improvement Plans, Grading and Staking Plans, Planting Plans
    Bell-Glazener Design Group; McKimmon, Edwards, and Associates; McKimmon, Edwards, & Shawcroft; Raleigh (N.C.)
  - Saint Mary's College, 1990-1991 (Tube 657)
    Staking and Grading Plans, Electrical Plans, Irrigation Plan, Planting Plans
  - Saint Mary's College, 1990-1997 (Tube 481)
    Master plan grid, Bratton Hall landscape improvements, central campus site
  - Saint Mary's College, 1991 (Tube 656)
    Irrigation Plan, Staking and Grading Plans, Site Plans (Base), Site Plans at Ravenscroft House (Base), Master Plans of North Central Campus, Detail of Portico and Fountain, Planting Plans
  - Saint Mary's College, 1991-1992 (Tube 659)
    Ravenscroft House Staking and Grading Plan, Site Plan, Relocation of Dean of Students residence Site Plan, Grading and Staking Plans, Detail Sheet, Planting Plan at Chapel and Surrounding Area Elevation of Wall and Fence on Saint Mary's Street, Planting Plans, Gate Details, Sketch
  - Saint Mary's College, 1991-1995 (Tube 480)
    Site development plan for new facility, planting and lighting, west parking lot, planting plan at chapel
  - Saint Mary's College (1 of 2), 1992 (Flatfolder 16)
    Existing master plans, steam tunnel plan, chilled water plan, fire protection plan, electrical plan, natural gas plan, telecommunications plan, storm sewer plan
  - Saint Mary's College (2 of 2), 1992 (Tube 662)
    Detail Sheets, Planting Plan, Master Plan of North Central Campus, Sketch
  - Saint Mary's College, 1992-1999 (Tube 162)
    Updated campus utility plan, updated master plan, topographic survey, revised infirmary, grading and staking plan
  - Saint Mary's College, 1993 (Flatfolder 9)
  - Saint Mary's College, 1993-1994 (Tube 655)
    Topographic Map, Master Plans of North Central Campus, Site Plan, Sidewalk Improvement Plan, West Parking Lot Site Plan, Grading and Staking Plan, Relocation of Dean of Students residence Site Plan, Chapel and Surrounding Area Planting Plans
    McKimmon, Edwards, and Associates; McKimmon, Edwards, & Shawcroft; Bell-Glazener Design Group; Raleigh (N.C.)
  - Saint Mary's College, 1994 (Tube 170)
    Site development plan for new facility, site utilization study - west campus, Cameron Park property
  - Saint Mary's College, 1994-1995 (Tube 236)
    Site development plan for new facility
  - Saint Mary's College, 1997 (Tube 179)
    Bratton Hall landscape improvements, campus lighting, storm drainage
  - Saint Mary's College, 1997-1999 (Tube 163)
    Master development plan, revised infirmary, staking plan, grading plan, storm drainage plan, details
    Bell-Glazener Design Group; Richard C. Bell Associates; Raleigh (N.C.)
  - Saint Mary's College (Tube 368)
    Campus plan
  - Saint Mary's College (Tube 130)
    Land Tech Surveyors, Inc.; Raleigh (N.C.)
  - Saint Mary's College (Tube 174)
    Land Tech Surveyors, Inc.; Bell-Glazener Design Group; Raleigh (N.C.)
  - Saint Mary's College: Central campus site improvement plans, 1989-1996 (Tube 462)
    Landscape Plans, Grading Plans, Construction Details
  - Saint Mary's College: Multi-purpose athletic field, 1993 (Tube 467)
    Grading Plan with Sedimentation/Erosion Control
  - Saint Mary's College/Saint Mary's School, 1971, 1993, 1997 (Tube 345)
    Grading plan with sediment/erosion control, revised front campus master plan, revised central campus plan, development plan, aerial photograph
    Richard C. Bell Associates; Bell-Glazener Design Group; Raleigh (N.C.)
  - Saint Mary's College/Saint Mary's School, 1989-1998 (Tube 369)
    Irrigation details, sesquicentennial project areas, site plan, landscape plan of bishop's residence, proposed landscape development plan, Ravenscroft House
  - Saint Mary's College/Saint Mary's School, 1997-1999 (Tube 347)
    Plan and details, master plan sketch, updated campus master plan
  - Saltworks Point, 1987 (Tube 13)
  - Sanderson High School, 1969 (Tube 784)
    Richard C. Bell Associates; Holloway-Reeves; Raleigh (N.C.)
  - Sandhu (Mr. and Mrs. Shabeg) residence, 1978 (Tube 283)
  - Sandy Forks Place Condominiums, 1999 (Tube 686)
  - Sandy Forks Place Condominiums (1 of 2), 1998-1999 (Tube 682)
    Utility plan, site plan, grading and erosion control plan, floor plans, elevations
    D. Miller & Associates, PA; Urena Steven M.; Raleigh (N.C.)
  - Sandy Forks Place Condominiums (2 of 2), 1998-1999 (Tube 683)
    Floor plans, plumbing plans, typical HVAC plan, lighting plan, power plan, site details
    Urena Steven M.; D. Miller & Associates, PA; Raleigh (N.C.)
  - Sanford (President and Mrs. Terry) residence: Duke University, 1970 (Tube 14)
  - Sarah P. Duke Memorial Gardens: Duke University, 1962 (Tube 828)
    Landscape Details and Typical Sections, Landscape Plan Elevations and Details at Yearby Street and Entrance, Landscape Plan at Yearby Street and Entrance, Landscape Plan and Details: Graduate Student Parking Area
  - Sawyer (Dr. and Mrs. L. Everett) residence, 1958 (Tube 56)
    Godwin and Bell, A.S.L.A.; Elizabeth City (N.C.)
  - Schematic Preliminary Projects NC 13.6 and NC 13.8, 1965 (Tube 52)
    M.A. Ham Associates; Richard C. Bell Associates; Carr, Harrison, Pruden & DePasquale
  - Scotland Memorial Hospital (Tube 722)
    Overall Site Plan, Detailed Site Plan
    Bell Design Group; Laurinburg (N.C.)
  - Scott (Mr. and Mrs. W. E.) residence, 1968 (Tube 768)
  - Seaboard Building: Renovations, 1987 (Tube 539)
    Herring Troy III AIA; Raleigh (N.C.)
  - Seale (Richard and Linda) residence (1 of 4), 1999 (Tube 97)
    Site development, landscape plan
    Bell-Glazener Design Group; Pine Knoll Shores (N.C.)
  - Seale (Richard and Linda) residence (2 of 4), 1999 (Tube 249)
    Site development and landscape plan
    Willis Architects; Bell-Glazener Design Group; Pine Knoll Shores (N.C.)
  - Seale (Richard and Linda) residence (3 of 4), 1999 (Tube 250)
  - Seale (Richard and Linda) residence (4 of 4), 1999 (Tube 98)
    Index, site plan, door schedule
    Willis Architects; Pine Knoll Shores (N.C.)
  - Sedgefield Development, 1987-1989 (Tube 663)
    Master Plan, Letter from Gary Hill to Richard Bell (9 August 1989)
    Evans Engineering, Inc.; Westminster Company; Bell-Glazener Design Group; Greensboro (N.C.)
  - Sedgefield Development, 1987 (Tube 666)
    Westminster Company; Evans Engineering, Inc.; Bell-Glazener Design Group; Greensboro (N.C.)
  - Shaw residence (Tube 97)
  - Shaw (Dr. and Mrs. Frank) residence, 1995 (Tube 468)
    Site Plans, Aerial Photographs, Topographic Survey
    Moorman, Kizer, and Reitzel, Inc.; Bell-Glazener Design Group; Cumberland County (N.C.)
  - Shaw (Mr. and Mrs. David) residence, 1976 (Tube 735)
    Preliminary Landscape Development, Plant List, Planting Notes and Details, Planting Plan
  - Sheraton Hotel and marina, New Bern waterfront, 1988 (Tube 166)
    Renovations and additions, selective demolition, staking and grading, planting plan, site construction details
    Bartholomew Associates; Bell-Glazener Design Group; New Bern (N.C.)
  - Sheraton marina (Tube 551)
    Robert M. Chiles, P.E., Engineers & Consultants; New Bern (N.C.)
  - Shields (Mr. and Mrs. Howard W.) residence, 1968 (Tube 52)
    Richard C. Bell Associates; Colvin, Hammill & Walter Associates; Winston-Salem (N.C.)
  - Sir Walter Chevrolet, 1994-1996 (Tube 86)
    Erosion control plan, site details, road improvements, preliminary site plan, preliminary landscape plan
    Envirotek, Inc.; Raleigh (N.C.)
  - Sir Walter Chevrolet Company (1 of 2), 1963 (Tube 440)
    Construction Plan and Details, Construction Details
  - Sir Walter Chevrolet Company (2 of 2), 1963 (Tube 447)
    Construction Plan and Designs, Site Plans
  - Site improvements at Seaboard parking area (1 of 2), 1992-1993 (Tube 460)
    Demolition/Staking Plans, Grading/Planting Plans
  - Site improvements at Seaboard parking area (2 of 2), 1992-1993 (Tube 466)
  - Six Forks office building, 1968 (Tube 784)
    Richard C. Bell Associates; McKimmon and Rogers; Raleigh (N.C.)
  - Smith and Smith Surveyors: Office building, 1976 (Tube 477)
    John Knox Smith Associates; Bell Design Group
  - Smith Subdivision property, 1954-1957 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Habel Fred W.; Raleigh (N.C.)
  - Smith-Dunaway Farm, 1973 (Tube 36)
  - Smith (Barbara and Dan Richards) residence, 1985 (Tube 320)
  - Smith (David H.) property, 1976 (Tube 744)
    Baker Derward W.; Wake County (N.C.)
  - Smith (Dr. and Mrs. E.H.) residence, 1962 (Tube 14)
  - Smith (Troy and Sally) residence, 1987 (Tube 298)
    Grading
    Robert W. Carr, Inc., Architects; Bell Design Group; New Bern (N.C.)
  - Smithfield-Selma Branch Goldsboro N.C. Stake (Tube 476)
    Planting plan, grading plan, site development
    Phillips & Associates, Architects; Bell Design Group
  - Snipes (Mr. and Mrs. C.L.) residence, 1973 (Tube 7)
  - Southeastern Flower and Garden Show (1 of 3), 1960 (Tube 164)
  - Southeastern Flower and Garden Show (2 of 3), 1960 (Tube 529)
  - Southeastern Flower and Garden Show (3 of 3), 1960 (Tube 768)
  - Southeastern Flower and Garden Show (1 of 2), 1962 (Tube 527)
    Plan and details
  - Southeastern Flower and Garden Show (2 of 2), 1962 (Tube 731)
  - Southeastern Flower and Garden Show (Tube 850)
    Master Plan, Garden No. 9, Garden No, 4, Details, Japanese Garden No. 6, Gardens 3 & 8
  - Southeastern Flower and Garden Show (Tube 768)
    Main Feature Garden, Main Nursery Garden 5th Annual
  - Southern Living Show (1 of 2), 1977-1978 (Tube 107)
    Kitchen plan
  - Southern Living Show (2 of 2), 1977-1978 (Tube 100)
    Greenhouse plan, kitchen elevations, plans
  - Southern Living Show (1 of 2), 1979 (Tube 167)
  - Southern Living Show (2 of 2), 1979 (Tube 169)
    Charlotte (N.C.)
  - Southern Living Show, 1980 (Tube 768)
    Sun-Earth Theme Design/Built Homes Details, Berm House Framing Plan and Details
  - Southern Living Show: Solar victory garden, solar green room, 1980 (Tube 51)
  - Southwood Condominium Townhouses (1 of 5), 1972 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    Sections, Pool Foundation
    Bell Design Group; Domus Associates Incorporated; Charlotte (N.C.)
  - Southwood Condominium Townhouses (2 of 5), 1972 (Tube 322)
  - Southwood Condominium Townhouses (3 of 5), 1972 (Tube 643)
    Courtyard details, elevations, development plan
  - Southwood Condominium Townhouses (4 of 5), 1972 (Tube 685)
    Club and pool area, pool and fountain details, courtyard details, tree planting plan
  - Southwood Condominium Townhouses (5 of 5), 1972 (Tube 679)
    Courtyard details, club and pool area, landscape development plan
  - Sparger Springs, 1986 (Tube 853)
    Entrance Sign and Fence, Elevations and Sections, Site Plan
    Cimarron Capital, Inc.; Bell Design Group; Durham (N.C.)
  - Sparger Springs, 1984 (Tube 859)
  - Spring Forest, 1998 (Tube 454)
    Capacity study, Mappers
    Raleigh (N.C.); Raleigh (N.C.)
  - Spyglass Hill, 1981 (Tube 352)
    Schematic design phase master plan
  - St. Mary's College (Tube 815)
    Land Tech Surveyors, Inc.; Hillsborough (N.C.)
  - St. Mary's College (1 of 2), 1989
    Elevation showing Hillsborough Street/St. Mary Street intersection
  - St. Mary's College (2 of 2), 1989 (Tube 893)
  - St. Mary's College, 1995 (Tube 539)
    Grading Plan, Site Development Plan for New Facility
  - St. Mary's College, 1992 (Tube 513)
    Topographic surveys, Revised Front Campus Master Plan Grading and Staking Plan, Master Plan of North Central Campus